‪SPOOKY IN LOVE
‪Get off me!
‪-Mr. Ma! Keep still!
‪-Get off me!
‪Go away!
‪You said you weren't afraid!
‪No! No!
‪Go away!
‪He's off your back now!
‪He's gone!
‪He's gone?
‪Do you see the kid?
‪Yes. I see him.
‪EPISODE 4
‪What…
‪I'll call it in.
‪Okay.
‪Hey, are you all right?
‪The back… In the back.
‪-The back.
‪-In the back?
‪-Look in the back.
‪-Hold on.
‪My boy. He's okay, isn't he?
‪He's…
‪He's okay, isn't he?
‪He's warm.
‪Good.
‪That's good.
‪EMERGENCY SERVICES
‪Gang-uk.
‪Oh, no. Hold on.
‪-There's someone here!
‪-Help!
‪-In here.
‪-Over here!
‪There's someone here! Over here!
‪-Where are they?
‪-In there.
‪The child is alive!
‪Her breathing is shallow. Get the oxygen!
‪Ju-young, Daddy will make lots of money
‪and buy you plenty of toys.
‪Be good and listen to Grandma, okay?
‪-Okay.
‪-Good.
‪-Do you like that toy that much, Da-young?
‪-Yes.
‪Ju-young.
‪You're the big brother,
‪so look after your sister.
‪We found an injured little girl.
‪Yes. We're loading her up.
‪-Get that for me.
‪-Careful.
‪All done.
‪Let's go.
‪When did all this start?
‪I was in a yacht accident
‪when I was in university.
‪Yeo-ri!
‪I stopped breathing completely.
‪Then miraculously, I came to.
‪But my friend who fell in with me…
‪didn't make it.
‪We have two different words
‪that mean "grave," depending on the shape.
‪Some have a high, rounded top,
‪which we call "bun."
‪If the body is buried underground
‪with a flat top, it's called "myo."
‪There are three different kinds
‪of high, rounded grave tops.
‪The most common type is…
‪After that,
‪-I kept seeing Ji-hwan, who had died.
‪-Ji-hwan.
‪What's the matter?
‪That's when it began.
‪-It's a lovely day.
‪-It is.
‪The weather is amazing.
‪-Did you have something to eat?
‪-No, not yet.
‪Ghosts that others couldn't see
‪appeared in front of me.
‪Are you all right?
‪-And anyone whose hands touched mine
‪-Thank you.
‪started seeing them.
‪What's that?
‪-She sees ghosts.
‪-She can see stuff.
‪"If you so much as touch Cheon Yeo-ri,
‪ghosts will latch onto you too."
‪"If you stick around her,
‪you'll ‪be ‪cursed ‪too."
‪Rumors like that started to spread.
‪Ever since then,
‪I've been living alone,
‪like a living ghost.
‪I tried to live a decent life though.
‪There's a lot you can do on your own.
‪Once you get used to it,
‪being alone isn't so bad.
‪I suspected you as an accomplice,
‪not knowing about your background.
‪I'm sorry.
‪I got you all wrong too,
‪when we first met.
‪What do we do now?
‪More ghosts will come for you.
‪It can't be helped.
‪What happened to the other people
‪you came in contact with?
‪From what I know,
‪I think they saw ghosts for about a month.
‪And after that?
‪After a month,
‪the ghosts will stop coming for you,
‪as long as you stay away from me.
‪I'm sorry for the trouble I caused.
‪Let's stay away from each other
‪as best we can.
‪If you're around me,
‪you might become miserable.
‪Why would you say that?
‪Bye then.
‪Wait.
‪This is day one.
‪The start of that one month.
‪But still…
‪I finally understand
‪what you meant
‪in Jeju Island.
‪Thank you.
‪I might be used to how things are,
‪but that doesn't mean I'm not afraid.
‪It must've been so hard to live with.
‪I'm exhausted.
‪Let me rest tonight.
‪I have a lot on my mind.
‪Will he be okay?
‪It'll be really hard at first.
‪Why…
‪-What was that about?
‪-I don't know.
‪What's so funny?
‪Your name.
‪Oh, my heart hurts…
‪CEO CHEON YEO-RI
‪I wasn't aware of this,
‪but apparently this is a thing.
‪PVC STICKER FOR CARS
‪Print some and put them in the kids' zone.
‪Yes, ma'am.
‪One more thing.
‪How old is your child now, Ms. Eom?
‪-Four years old.
‪-I see.
‪In that case…
‪If your child happens to like
‪toys or dolls…
‪Thank you.
‪Prosecutor Ma Gang-uk?
‪Yes.
‪I think they've been in touch
‪ever since he came here to see her.
‪Are you saying they're dating?
‪I can't say for sure.
‪Okay.
‪What's all this?
‪Mr. Ma.
‪I thought you had no religion.
‪I converted to polytheism.
‪-Polytheism?
‪-Yeah.
‪Are you trying to integrate all religions?
‪You believe in all this?
‪Who knows which one actually counts?
‪There's bound to be one
‪that'll scare them.
‪Who exactly are you trying to scare?
‪Well, the punks I deal with
‪are a dangerous bunch.
‪You never know when
‪and which deity will come through.
‪You do look like you could use some faith.
‪Why don't you come over this weekend?
‪I'll keep you entertained.
‪Oh, my mom's calling.
‪-Hello? Hi, Mom.
‪-You know,
‪that's a completely ridiculous idea.
‪It's the weekend.
‪If I were to suddenly go crazy,
‪then maybe I'd visit.
‪You're right.
‪Weekends are precious.
‪Night duty is better than going home.
‪I'll see you in the office.
‪I do wonder what you do on weekends.
‪What should we do?
‪Do you play video games? Or board games?
‪Not board games.
‪Let's watch a movie.
‪Something really steamy.
‪-I can't wait.
‪-Good.
‪I'm excited.
‪I can't wait.
‪Don't laugh.
‪You call this steamy?
‪It's a darn old movie too.
‪You called me over just to watch this?
‪Come on, I need to build up some courage.
‪Help me out with some moral support.
‪Pil-dong.
‪Why do ghosts appear
‪in girls' high schools?
‪Well, I mean…
‪wouldn't it be ridiculous
‪if they were to haunt boys' schools?
‪Pil-dong, why do ghosts
‪always cling to people's backs?
‪Well…
‪If they were to cling to people
‪from the front like this,
‪wouldn't that look ridiculous?
‪Pil-dong, why do ghosts
‪have straight hair?
‪Do you think ghosts
‪would get perms
‪to keep the curls bouncy?
‪Wouldn't that look ridiculous?
‪You're right.
‪Could you just think
‪before you ask a question?
‪-Pil-dong.
‪-What?
‪What is it now?
‪You wanted to watch a movie.
‪It's a sunny Saturday afternoon,
‪and the two of us guys
‪are watching a goddamn movie.
‪-I'm leaving.
‪-What?
‪You threatened me
‪with night duty to come here,
‪-but I can't stand being with you.
‪-Pil-dong, it's not like that.
‪He thinks I'm his lackey
‪-since I'm at his beck and call.
‪-Pil-dong.
‪-Wait, I'll buy you tuna sashimi.
‪-I'm not some lackey.
‪I'll order it right now.
‪-I want some belly meat.
‪-Of course.
‪-I only eat Pacific bluefin.
‪-Right, of course.
‪Pacific bluefin.
‪Belly.
‪Pil-dong, wait for me!
‪It's only been a week.
‪It's almost time.
‪Right.
‪Let's go.
‪PROSECUTOR MA
‪Yeo-ri, please, please pick up.
‪Sorry.
‪It's best that you and I
‪don't cross paths,
‪not even over the phone.
‪The call cannot be connected.
‪You will be redirected to voicemail…
‪Ms. Cheon! Yeo-ri!
‪What the heck?
‪Who is it?
‪-I'll leave your package out here.
‪-Okay.
‪It's just the delivery man.
‪Yeo-ri.
‪Wait, why is it closing?
‪If someone calls, at least pick up.
‪I have so many things to ask you.
‪Ms. Cheon.
‪Yeo-ri.
‪I'm sorry.
‪I think this is for the best.
‪I came all the way here.
‪Can't we talk inside?
‪It's tough, isn't it?
‪I could barely get through a week.
‪How did you manage to endure it
‪for ten whole years?
‪To tell you the truth,
‪I blamed you at first, and I was furious.
‪So I came here to complain.
‪But seeing you here,
‪I realize how cowardly and pathetic I am.
‪Unlike you,
‪I just have to hold out for a month.
‪Compared to you,
‪my suffering is a drop in the ocean.
‪Sorry for coming all this way
‪and making a fuss.
‪Don't be.
‪I feel bad for you just the same.
‪I'll try to get through it on my own.
‪I'm an adult, after all.
‪Much more so than you were back then.
‪Bye then.
‪Wait.
‪How about…
‪we try this?
‪I don't know if it'll help,
‪but I have a few tips of my ‪own.
‪The ghosts that visit you early on
‪will be the nasty ones
‪that harass and torment others.
‪But don't let it show.
‪Their favorite moment ‪is
‪when ‪you ‪wake ‪up from sleep paralysis.
‪Do your best to hide that you're scared
‪and try to sleep as if you don't care.
‪Make them see that you're not affected.
‪Why? Is it not working tonight?
‪That's strange.
‪He's not usually like this.
‪I'm sure he saw us though.
‪Have you spoken to them?
‪Good.
‪Avoid talking to them at all costs.
‪Ignore them ‪and ‪hang ‪in ‪there
‪for as long as you can.
‪Good job.
‪What's wrong?
‪You must be at a crosswalk.
‪What do I do? He's staring at me.
‪Step on the gas as if you don't see him.
‪What?
‪-Do it.
‪-But…
‪The more you know,
‪the more you can handle.
‪I lose.
‪PROSECUTOR MA GANG-UK
‪I'm almost there. It's nearly over.
‪I just have to last one more week.
‪-Oh, right.
‪-What? What is it now?
‪I got distracted and forgot the basics.
‪Sprinkling salt.
‪Hurl it down hard, with force.
‪Garlic.
‪-Hey, Ma.
‪-No, thanks.
‪-Hi.
‪-Sit with us.
‪I have to go through something.
‪-Enjoy yourselves.
‪-What?
‪I hear they dislike food
‪with strong odors or flavors.
‪In that sense, garlic is very effective.
‪He's definitely acting a bit off.
‪He's lost it.
‪He keeps asking me things like,
‪"Why do ghosts always
‪have long, straight hair?"
‪"Why do they cling to one's back?"
‪There must be something about ghosts.
‪Could he be possessed?
‪Look.
‪Look at him stuffing his face
‪with all that garlic.
‪-What's going on?
‪-What's gotten into him?
‪You know, in movies,
‪people who are possessed
‪stuff garlic down, then spit it out.
‪That's Dracula. Vampires do that.
‪-Oh, right.
‪-Korean ghosts hate glutinous rice
‪-and red beans.
‪-Right.
‪-It's the prosecutor general.
‪-I'm disturbing you all.
‪It's fine. Stay seated.
‪Let's eat over there.
‪Which division are you in?
‪Yes, sir. I'm…
‪I'm in the Cold Case Unit.
‪My name is Ma Gang-uk, sir.
‪Oh, the team they decided to revamp?
‪Yes.
‪-So, sir.
‪-Mr. Ma.
‪I appreciate the intention
‪behind revamping the Cold Case Unit.
‪But the recent personnel transfer
‪was influenced by an outside…
‪-I'm so sorry.
‪-Clean him up.
‪I'm sorry, sir.
‪-Sir, let me…
‪-Oh, dear.
‪I'm so sorry, sir. I was…
‪He definitely did spit it out.
‪Oh, gosh.
‪Yeo-ri.
‪Show me your glass and champagne too.
‪What do you mean?
‪It'll be all over by tomorrow night.
‪Let's celebrate with champagne,
‪even if it's over a video call.
‪Give me a moment.
‪It's like we're drinking alone,
‪but not quite.
‪They say you shouldn't
‪pop the champagne too early though.
‪It'll be fine.
‪What could happen in just one day?
‪As long as there aren't too many of them,
‪I'm sure I can manage on my own for a day.
‪Shall we?
‪-Cheers.
‪Yeo-ri.
‪Thank you for everything.
‪I'm glad if I helped beat the fear.
‪You didn't. I was scared the whole time.
‪What?
‪I was scared the whole time.
‪They have no physical form,
‪and they're not human,
‪so how could I not be scared?
‪That's true.
‪The truth is,
‪I feel the same,
‪though I pretend not to be.
‪Right?
‪So I wasn't the only one to be scared.
‪As soon as one ghost leaves,
‪another one appears.
‪And why are there so many different kinds?
‪I was terrified every single time.
‪But I felt reassured…
‪by your voice
‪that helped me through each time.
‪That's how I was able to get through it.
‪I guess that means I protected you, right?
‪That's pretty rewarding.
‪Thank you, Yeo-ri.
‪Oh, and I did some thinking.
‪Wouldn't it be okay
‪to interact virtually like this?
‪We can check on each other sometimes,
‪or ask for help if we need it.
‪People make friends
‪through social media these days,
‪and even travel online
‪without being there.
‪No.
‪It's best if we don't do that.
‪If you just get through one more day,
‪we can both return
‪to our everyday lives, right?
‪Take care of yourself.
‪Even if we meet by chance,
‪let's pretend…
‪to be strangers.
‪Yeo-ri…
‪Bye.
‪CEO CHEON YEO-RI
‪CALL ENDED
‪Wasn't that a bit too harsh?
‪We'll pretend to be strangers
‪even if we meet by chance?
‪Thank you for everything.
‪I was terrified every single time.
‪But I felt reassured
‪by your voice
‪that helped me through each time.
‪That's how I was able to get through it.
‪You said you could manage
‪on your own for a day.
‪What ghost is it this time?
‪CHEON HA-RI
‪Why do you care who I'm talking to?
‪And don't even think of
‪bringing me down with that again.
‪"What ghost is it this time?"
‪She's definitely hiding something.
‪-Min-hwan.
‪-Ha-ri.
‪I'm so touched.
‪You offered to treat me,
‪and you actually came.
‪What?
‪Oh, sure. Is there anything you'd like?
‪Whatever you like is fine.
‪You're a gourmand.
‪By the way, is something up with Yeo-ri?
‪What?
‪I called her a few times since I came,
‪but she didn't pick up.
‪If she doesn't pick up,
‪she's putting up a wall.
‪From what my mom told me,
‪she seems to be seeing
‪some prosecutor pretty often.
‪Prosecutor Ma Gang-uk?
‪How do you know his name?
‪Ha-ri.
‪If you care about someone,
‪you naturally learn all about them.
‪PRO GOLFER PARK'S EX JANG FOUND DEAD
‪PARK WANTED AS LIKELY SUSPECT
‪Damn it!
‪So Cheon Yeo-ri reported it,
‪and that's how Ma found out?
‪I'm sure of it.
‪No wonder they both went on
‪about my monumental fall.
‪Seung-jae.
‪What you said before.
‪-Did you mean that?
‪-About what?
‪You swore on your life
‪that you'd help me take over Reina
‪once you get out of here.
‪You bet I did.
‪Then do just one thing for me.
‪Then you won't have to bother
‪swearing on your life
‪for Cheon Yeo-ri
‪to lose my grandma's favor.
‪It'll ruin her chances
‪of becoming a successor too.
‪What do you say?
‪Mr. Ma.
‪What? I'm going to leave on time today.
‪It's not that.
‪It's Park Seung-jae.
‪What about him?
‪Park Seung-jae was granted
‪a motion for detention review?
‪Why do you care?
‪It's not your case anymore.
‪It may not be my case, but still.
‪It makes no sense that a murderer like him
‪is getting released!
‪You think I granted it? The court did!
‪SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
‪It was the prosecutor general's order.
‪He has high hopes for the Cold Case Unit.
‪Do a good job and score some points.
‪And be gentle with the door
‪when you come and go.
‪CORRECTIONAL SERVICES
‪ADVANCING ORDER AND HUMAN RIGHTS
‪-Well done.
‪-Good job.
‪Man, I had the worst time in there.
‪Hey, Park Seung-jae.
‪What now?
‪I was released by the law
‪that you love so much.
‪I know your father got you out.
‪It's my luck to have such a father.
‪Yes, I know that too.
‪I also know your father spent millions
‪to make you a golfer,
‪and that you won the first trial
‪thanks to his connections.
‪Man, getting screwed over like that
‪made me fixate on something.
‪What might that be?
‪I got some meaty intel
‪about a reservoir
‪your father's slush fund is buried.
‪Why you…
‪Watch your back.
‪You could get hurt
‪if you go after the wrong person.
‪You watch your own back.
‪I have nothing to lose
‪because my job isn't my whole life.
‪I guess I'd get no joy going after
‪a guy like you, just scraping by.
‪I plan to find a weakness
‪instead of going after you.
‪What are you on about?
‪Cheon Yeo-ri.
‪I just said her name.
‪What's with that look?
‪Why would you bring her up right now?
‪Wouldn't you love to know?
‪Let's get going.
‪CEO CHEON YEO-RI
‪Even if we meet by chance,
‪let's pretend to be strangers.
‪Yes, ma'am.
‪I saw your message. Is something wrong?
‪The Ministry of Foreign Affairs
‪called about the venue selection
‪for the GA21 banquet.
‪The inspection is in two days, right?
‪They asked ‪if ‪it ‪could ‪be ‪moved up
‪to tomorrow instead.
‪May I confirm with them?
‪Go ahead. We're fully prepared anyway.
‪-Will do, ma'am.
‪-Bye.
‪PROSECUTOR MA
‪Who are you?
‪Do I look like the Grim Reaper to you?
‪Why are you digging a hole
‪in the middle of the night?
‪I wanted to bury it right away.
‪The clay jar with kimchi I just made.
‪Why bury it outside
‪when I have a fridge for that?
‪Besides, let your goons do the hard work.
‪They look like experts at that.
‪Watch how you talk.
‪I made this for you.
‪I wouldn't let
‪anyone's grimy hands touch it.
‪I'm worried you'll hurt your hips.
‪Let's go inside.
‪Are you worried I'll get hurt?
‪Of course I'm worried.
‪Here you go.
‪No fridge can store food
‪as well as a clay jar.
‪That's true. Plus, your touch works magic.
‪Right?
‪Try this too.
‪-Here.
‪-Oh, thanks.
‪You really weren't in Jeju Island?
‪I swear I saw you.
‪Why do you keep asking
‪when I wasn't there?
‪Remember how
‪-you told me to beware of water?
‪-Yeah.
‪The crazy thing is,
‪I fell into the sea that day.
‪There's no need to be so shocked.
‪I can swim as well as anyone.
‪Don't you know that even
‪the best of people make mistakes?
‪I do know that.
‪So why did you fall into the water?
‪Well…
‪I slipped and lost my footing.
‪I told you to be careful.
‪-I will.
‪-Goodness…
‪-Anyway,
‪-Oh, dear.
‪the Year of the Black Monkey
‪you keep talking about.
‪Did you hear that from a fortune-teller?
‪Why?
‪Are you seeing someone born in that year?
‪Why would you say that?
‪I'm not seeing anyone.
‪-I'm not.
‪-You're not, right?
‪But what's the deal
‪with that specific year?
‪There's nothing wrong
‪with the year itself.
‪The problem is
‪that it's incompatible with you.
‪Remember that.
‪Okay, fine. Eat up.
‪-One more thing.
‪-What?
‪Don't go anywhere tonight.
‪Stay out of harm's way.
‪Okay.
‪You shouldn't cook so much.
‪You said your wrists hurt.
‪-I'll order delivery. It's just as good.
‪-Enough.
‪Delivery, my foot. Just eat.
‪It must be my grandma's energy.
‪I don't see any ghosts.
‪Or is it because it's the last day?
‪Oh, dear.
‪I plan to find a weakness.
‪Cheon Yeo-ri.
‪Why would you bring her up right now?
‪Wouldn't you love to know?
‪CEO CHEON YEO-RI
‪The phone is turned off.
‪You will be redirected to voicemail…
‪Grandma?
‪-That hurts.
‪-I told you not to go anywhere!
‪Why won't you listen?
‪Goodness.
‪Stay right there.
‪Jeez.
‪She's so strong for her age.
‪Does she know something
‪or is it just a hunch?
‪Why did Cheon Yeo-ri
‪turn off her phone anyway?
‪I feel nasty
‪because I only washed my hair earlier.
‪I'll just take a shower
‪and go straight to bed, okay?
‪Don't take too long.
‪-Why you…
‪-Go to bed.
‪Don't you dare go out.
‪I won't.
‪Hi.
‪You're out of your mind.
‪You're only adding to your charges.
‪That's for me to take care of.
‪I heard you ratted me out.
‪Park Seung-jae.
‪That's not called ratting out.
‪It's called reporting a crime.
‪Whatever you call it, you still did it.
‪How did you know where Jang Eun-ju was?
‪You really want to know that badly?
‪Yes, I do.
‪Ha-ri's right, isn't she?
‪You see ghosts, don't you?
‪F**D M*
‪I heard Shaman Baek suppressed it,
‪but it didn't work, did it?
‪Whether I see ghosts or not,
‪how is that worth kidnapping me?
‪It is worth kidnapping you.
‪You see,
‪it was Ha-ri's condition.
‪She put you up to this?
‪She said to bring back proof
‪that you can see ghosts.
‪But that's not going to cut it.
‪I need something more
‪so you taste the monumental fall yourself.
‪From what I heard,
‪there will be a big scandal out soon
‪about a drug party with celebrities
‪and rich heirs and heiresses.
‪I'm going to make sure
‪that your name is on the list.
‪It'll be a little leverage
‪to keep you quiet.
‪You crazy…
‪Here.
‪What's this punk doing?
‪-Are you all right?
‪-Mr. Ma.
‪Get up.
‪Let's go.
‪Get them, damn it!
‪-How did you find me?
‪-Let's get out of here first.
‪Damn it!
‪Shit!
‪Mr. Ma!
‪-Gang-uk.
‪-Mr. Ma.
‪-Oh, no.
‪-Mr. Ma!
‪Are you okay?
‪-Call for help!
‪-Quick, call an ambulance!
‪-Are you all right?
‪-Don't touch him.
‪Careful.
‪-The ambulance!
‪-Did you call for one?
‪Tell them to hurry!
‪-Wake up! There's blood…
‪-Don't move him.
‪Mr. Ma, wake up.
‪Mr. Ma.
‪Mr. Ma!
‪He's a traffic accident victim.
‪Found unconscious, BP is 80 over 40.
‪O2 saturation went down to 89,
‪so we put him on oxygen.
‪Mr. Ma! Hurry!
‪Mr. Ma!
‪Please, Mr. Ma.
‪-Mr. Ma.
‪-Wait outside.
‪-You can't come in! Stay here!
‪-Mr. Ma!
‪-Okay.
‪-Sir?
‪Do you hear me?
‪Sir. What's your name?
‪-Check for a pulse.
‪-Okay.
‪He's in Ventricular tachycardia.
‪Starting CPR.
‪-Get a defibrillator.
‪-Okay.
‪-What's wrong? Why are they doing that?
‪-Damn it.
‪-What are they doing?
‪-You can't come in.
‪Take good care of him! Please save him!
‪Mr. Ma!
‪Let's change places.
‪Gang-uk!
‪Gang-uk…
‪Mr. Ma!
‪It's my fault.
‪Because of me…
‪I could barely get through a week.
‪How did you manage to endure it
‪for ten whole years?
‪I'll try to get through it on my own.
‪I'm an adult, after all.
‪Much more so than you were back then.
‪Here.
‪Let's stay away from each other
‪as best we can.
‪If you're around me,
‪you might become miserable.
‪Mr. Ma.
‪I suspected you as an accomplice,
‪not knowing about your background.
‪I'm sorry.
‪It must've been so hard to live with.
‪Mr. Ma?
‪Gang-uk.
‪Oh, no…
‪Because of me,
‪you turned into a ghost already
‪and came to see me?
‪Oh, no…
‪Oh, gosh…
‪SPOOKY IN LOVE
‪Reporters are already
‪swarming ‪outside Reina.
‪Should there be any
‪speculative articles or photos,
‪we will take strong legal action,
‪so please step back.
‪They're birds of a feather.
‪Are you doing this ‪because
‪you ‪really want to marry Min-hwan?
‪Cheon Ha-ri.
‪Director Ok,
‪should we acquire another masterpiece?
‪Yeeon Museum of Art.
‪The director there is pretty influential.
‪Reina Hotel's slush fund allegations?
‪The artworks displayed at the hotel
‪are supplied by Gallery Cheon, right?
‪How much do you know ‪about ‪Yeo-ri?
‪Don't you want to know?
‪Some rumors started
‪after the engagement fell through.
‪Who's there?
‪A bastard like him
‪doesn't deserve to be human.
‪Who are you? Who the hell are you?
‪-Let go.
‪-Damn it.
‪I'll make you regret this.
‪Subtitle translation by: Jennifer Jean Lim